The streetlights make a blurry line
I'm running through the same old signs
I'm just a face in a passing crowd
Afraid to speak my thoughts out loud
But then you found me in the noise
You heard a whisper in my voice
You gave me something to believe
A reason I would never leave
If you walked away The sky would lose its blue I
wouldn't know what to do I'd be lonely If you
walked away, my world would fall apart.
They build these walls so high and steep
With promises they never keep
But we have a fortress strong and true
I'm safe as long as I have you. If you walked away,
the sky would lose its blue. I wouldn't know what
to do. I'd be lost in the gray. If you walked away,
my world would fall apart.
I'm holding
on,
I'm holding tight
Don't let me go into the night
If you walked away The sky would lose its blue I
wouldn't know what to do I'd be lost Lost in the
grey If you walked away My world would fall apart
You're the owner of my
own heart
Don't walk away